statsdomain.com 2016-03-27

# Privacy Policy of StatsDomain

## StatsDomain Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy was last modified on September 10, 2015.

StatsDomain ("us", "we", or "our") operates statsdomain.com (the "Site"). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site.

We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible at statsdomain.com.

**Information Collection And Use**  
While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to, your name, email address, postal address and phone number ("Personal Information").

**Log Data**  
Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

### Cookies

To make this site work properly, we sometimes place small data files called cookies on your device. Most big websites do this too. 

**What are cookies?**

A cookie is a small text file that a website saves on your computer or mobile device when you visit the site. It enables the website to remember your actions and preferences (such as login, language, font size and other display preferences) over a period of time, so you don’t have to keep re-entering them whenever you come back to the site or browse from one page to another. 

**How do we use cookies?**

A number of our pages use cookies to: 

  * Help remember and process the items in the shopping cart.
  * Understand and save user's preferences for future visits.
  * Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third party services that track this information on our behalf. 

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

**Google**

**If users disable cookies in their browser:**

If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled It will turn off some of the features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. 

**Security**  
The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**Links To Other Sites**  
Our Site may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

StatsDomain has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for, the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party sites or services.

**Google Analytics**   
Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google. Google utilizes the data collected to track and examine the use of statsdomain.com, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services. Google may use the data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. We may use the 3rd-party audience data (such as age, gender, and interests) by Google Analytics, to analyze and provide a much better service through our website.

**Advertising**   
Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Google Adsense**   
Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses "non personally identifiable information" and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

**Changes To This Privacy Policy**  
StatsDomain may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Site. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes.

**Contact Us**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
